{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651259154","data":{"timestamp":" 947651259153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651259387","data":{"timestamp":" 947651259387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651260359","data":{"timestamp":" 947651260358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651261645","data":{"timestamp":" 947651261644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651264555","data":{"timestamp":" 947651264555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651265398","data":{"timestamp":" 947651265398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651265711","data":{"timestamp":" 947651265711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651266945","data":{"timestamp":" 947651266944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651270435","data":{"timestamp":" 947651270435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651271426","data":{"timestamp":" 947651271426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651271680","data":{"timestamp":" 947651271680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651272631","data":{"timestamp":" 947651272631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651275494","data":{"timestamp":" 947651275493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651276540","data":{"timestamp":" 947651276540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651277018","data":{"timestamp":" 947651277018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651281607","data":{"timestamp":" 947651281604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651281763","data":{"timestamp":" 947651281763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 3d8ef7ff-0886-413e-a783-236e2a396d52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652386872","data":{"timestamp":" 947652386872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652388036","data":{"timestamp":" 947652388035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652391923","data":{"timestamp":" 947652391923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652396847","data":{"timestamp":" 947652396847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652405862","data":{"timestamp":" 947652405862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652413040","data":{"timestamp":" 947652413040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652425324","data":{"timestamp":" 947652425324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652431575","data":{"timestamp":" 947652431575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652434268","data":{"timestamp":" 947652434268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652436884","data":{"timestamp":" 947652436884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652440109","data":{"timestamp":" 947652440109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652443532","data":{"timestamp":" 947652443532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652445159","data":{"timestamp":" 947652445159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652449445","data":{"timestamp":" 947652449445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652452519","data":{"timestamp":" 947652452519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIENDESHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652458352","data":{"timestamp":" 947652458352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEREMKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652462335","data":{"timestamp":" 947652462335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652464298","data":{"timestamp":" 947652464298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652484144","data":{"timestamp":" 947652484144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652490912","data":{"timestamp":" 947652490912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652495815","data":{"timestamp":" 947652495815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652504599","data":{"timestamp":" 947652504599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652510060","data":{"timestamp":" 947652510060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652517263","data":{"timestamp":" 947652517263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652520420","data":{"timestamp":" 947652520418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652522922","data":{"timestamp":" 947652522922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652524964","data":{"timestamp":" 947652524963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652526892","data":{"timestamp":" 947652526892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652531337","data":{"timestamp":" 947652531337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652535732","data":{"timestamp":" 947652535732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652540521","data":{"timestamp":" 947652540521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652543335","data":{"timestamp":" 947652543335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652548329","data":{"timestamp":" 947652548328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652551193","data":{"timestamp":" 947652551193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652553782","data":{"timestamp":" 947652553781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652555715","data":{"timestamp":" 947652555715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652557657","data":{"timestamp":" 947652557657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652559305","data":{"timestamp":" 947652559305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652562415","data":{"timestamp":" 947652562415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNUNU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652564470","data":{"timestamp":" 947652564470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652575781","data":{"timestamp":" 947652575781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZINGATIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652578816","data":{"timestamp":" 947652578816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652582484","data":{"timestamp":" 947652582484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652587132","data":{"timestamp":" 947652587132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIGONGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652591696","data":{"timestamp":" 947652591696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652598202","data":{"timestamp":" 947652598202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652599913","data":{"timestamp":" 947652599913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652602333","data":{"timestamp":" 947652602333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652604289","data":{"timestamp":" 947652604289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652606198","data":{"timestamp":" 947652606198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652610169","data":{"timestamp":" 947652610169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652612504","data":{"timestamp":" 947652612504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652614883","data":{"timestamp":" 947652614882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652616679","data":{"timestamp":" 947652616678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652618352","data":{"timestamp":" 947652618351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652618853","data":{"timestamp":" 947652618853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652620835","data":{"timestamp":" 947652620835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652624350","data":{"timestamp":" 947652624349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652626661","data":{"timestamp":" 947652626660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652628648","data":{"timestamp":" 947652628648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652630624","data":{"timestamp":" 947652630623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652633166","data":{"timestamp":" 947652633166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652638256","data":{"timestamp":" 947652638256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652641067","data":{"timestamp":" 947652641067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652643405","data":{"timestamp":" 947652643405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652645203","data":{"timestamp":" 947652645203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652649400","data":{"timestamp":" 947652649400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652650959","data":{"timestamp":" 947652650959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652653872","data":{"timestamp":" 947652653872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652656793","data":{"timestamp":" 947652656793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULITISHIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652660572","data":{"timestamp":" 947652660572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652662585","data":{"timestamp":" 947652662582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652662750","data":{"timestamp":" 947652662750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652679291","data":{"timestamp":" 947652679291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 65bd308c-ded6-40fa-ad8b-f5a454091c35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652696124","data":{"timestamp":" 947652696123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652698533","data":{"timestamp":" 947652698533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652700623","data":{"timestamp":" 947652700623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652702907","data":{"timestamp":" 947652702907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652705692","data":{"timestamp":" 947652705692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652707863","data":{"timestamp":" 947652707862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652710183","data":{"timestamp":" 947652710183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652712161","data":{"timestamp":" 947652712161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652713958","data":{"timestamp":" 947652713958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652715711","data":{"timestamp":" 947652715711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652719307","data":{"timestamp":" 947652719307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652723041","data":{"timestamp":" 947652723041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652725348","data":{"timestamp":" 947652725348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652727985","data":{"timestamp":" 947652727985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652731431","data":{"timestamp":" 947652731431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652734496","data":{"timestamp":" 947652734496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652736960","data":{"timestamp":" 947652736960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652740417","data":{"timestamp":" 947652740417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652743605","data":{"timestamp":" 947652743605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652746102","data":{"timestamp":" 947652746102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652747860","data":{"timestamp":" 947652747860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652750459","data":{"timestamp":" 947652750459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652755743","data":{"timestamp":" 947652755743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652757838","data":{"timestamp":" 947652757836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652760711","data":{"timestamp":" 947652760711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPALILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652763191","data":{"timestamp":" 947652763191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652765679","data":{"timestamp":" 947652765679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652767755","data":{"timestamp":" 947652767755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652772069","data":{"timestamp":" 947652772069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652774183","data":{"timestamp":" 947652774183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652778863","data":{"timestamp":" 947652778863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652784535","data":{"timestamp":" 947652784535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652786499","data":{"timestamp":" 947652786499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652788556","data":{"timestamp":" 947652788555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652793377","data":{"timestamp":" 947652793377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652795522","data":{"timestamp":" 947652795521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652805156","data":{"timestamp":" 947652805156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947652807148","data":{"timestamp":" 947652807148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653045439","data":{"timestamp":" 947653045439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653052455","data":{"timestamp":" 947653052455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653566062","data":{"timestamp":" 947653566061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 13735701-58a8-45e3-bbfb-f042a71d4c74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653566065","data":{"timestamp":" 947653566065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 45d526ab-3eff-4fe6-b3c4-9b17d42e0e4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653590713","data":{"timestamp":" 947653590713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653597512","data":{"timestamp":" 947653597512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653602682","data":{"timestamp":" 947653602681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653607750","data":{"timestamp":" 947653607750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653610191","data":{"timestamp":" 947653610191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653616341","data":{"timestamp":" 947653616341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653621220","data":{"timestamp":" 947653621220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653626514","data":{"timestamp":" 947653626514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653630897","data":{"timestamp":" 947653630897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653634113","data":{"timestamp":" 947653634113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653634421","data":{"timestamp":" 947653634420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" e807eabe-1425-4ec9-bccf-5e8b0d2e098a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653644893","data":{"timestamp":" 947653644893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653645115","data":{"timestamp":" 947653645115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653646080","data":{"timestamp":" 947653646080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653647352","data":{"timestamp":" 947653647352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653650270","data":{"timestamp":" 947653650270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653651128","data":{"timestamp":" 947653651128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653651451","data":{"timestamp":" 947653651451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653652708","data":{"timestamp":" 947653652708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653656242","data":{"timestamp":" 947653656241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653657228","data":{"timestamp":" 947653657228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653657490","data":{"timestamp":" 947653657489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653658438","data":{"timestamp":" 947653658438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653661294","data":{"timestamp":" 947653661294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653662328","data":{"timestamp":" 947653662328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653662806","data":{"timestamp":" 947653662805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653667372","data":{"timestamp":" 947653667372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653667443","data":{"timestamp":" 947653667443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 76e27176-053d-41b9-855c-9ca331d42102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653678850","data":{"timestamp":" 947653678850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653680914","data":{"timestamp":" 947653680914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653683200","data":{"timestamp":" 947653683200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653685399","data":{"timestamp":" 947653685399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653687332","data":{"timestamp":" 947653687331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653689253","data":{"timestamp":" 947653689253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653692048","data":{"timestamp":" 947653692048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653694210","data":{"timestamp":" 947653694210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653696100","data":{"timestamp":" 947653696100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653697394","data":{"timestamp":" 947653697394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653699947","data":{"timestamp":" 947653699947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653701833","data":{"timestamp":" 947653701833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653703774","data":{"timestamp":" 947653703773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653705847","data":{"timestamp":" 947653705847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPENZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653707652","data":{"timestamp":" 947653707652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653709879","data":{"timestamp":" 947653709879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653711903","data":{"timestamp":" 947653711903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653713817","data":{"timestamp":" 947653713817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653716771","data":{"timestamp":" 947653716771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653718279","data":{"timestamp":" 947653718279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653720485","data":{"timestamp":" 947653720485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653722343","data":{"timestamp":" 947653722343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653724561","data":{"timestamp":" 947653724561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653727068","data":{"timestamp":" 947653727068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMETAMETA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653730384","data":{"timestamp":" 947653730384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653733690","data":{"timestamp":" 947653733690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653737882","data":{"timestamp":" 947653737882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653740674","data":{"timestamp":" 947653740674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653742667","data":{"timestamp":" 947653742667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653745715","data":{"timestamp":" 947653745715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653748122","data":{"timestamp":" 947653748122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONEKANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653750637","data":{"timestamp":" 947653750637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653753206","data":{"timestamp":" 947653753206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653754755","data":{"timestamp":" 947653754755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653756746","data":{"timestamp":" 947653756745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIANGALIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653760047","data":{"timestamp":" 947653760046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653761964","data":{"timestamp":" 947653761964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653763839","data":{"timestamp":" 947653763839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653765846","data":{"timestamp":" 947653765846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653768929","data":{"timestamp":" 947653768928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653772705","data":{"timestamp":" 947653772705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653775488","data":{"timestamp":" 947653775488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653778463","data":{"timestamp":" 947653778463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653780579","data":{"timestamp":" 947653780579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653783189","data":{"timestamp":" 947653783189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653785602","data":{"timestamp":" 947653785602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653789686","data":{"timestamp":" 947653789686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653793986","data":{"timestamp":" 947653793986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKILIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653796708","data":{"timestamp":" 947653796707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653799382","data":{"timestamp":" 947653799381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653802497","data":{"timestamp":" 947653802497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653804750","data":{"timestamp":" 947653804749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653806997","data":{"timestamp":" 947653806997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWEKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653808647","data":{"timestamp":" 947653808647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653810575","data":{"timestamp":" 947653810575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653813858","data":{"timestamp":" 947653813858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653816537","data":{"timestamp":" 947653816537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653818601","data":{"timestamp":" 947653818600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653820777","data":{"timestamp":" 947653820777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653822788","data":{"timestamp":" 947653822788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653825099","data":{"timestamp":" 947653825099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653827012","data":{"timestamp":" 947653827012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653828863","data":{"timestamp":" 947653828863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FYATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653832089","data":{"timestamp":" 947653832089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653834193","data":{"timestamp":" 947653834192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653835968","data":{"timestamp":" 947653835967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653837423","data":{"timestamp":" 947653837423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653840031","data":{"timestamp":" 947653840031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653842204","data":{"timestamp":" 947653842204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653844056","data":{"timestamp":" 947653844055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653846669","data":{"timestamp":" 947653846669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653849986","data":{"timestamp":" 947653849986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653852010","data":{"timestamp":" 947653852010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653853948","data":{"timestamp":" 947653853948"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653856190","data":{"timestamp":" 947653856190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653857983","data":{"timestamp":" 947653857983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653859956","data":{"timestamp":" 947653859956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653866714","data":{"timestamp":" 947653866714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPOANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653868725","data":{"timestamp":" 947653868725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEMKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653871148","data":{"timestamp":" 947653871148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653873143","data":{"timestamp":" 947653873143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653874431","data":{"timestamp":" 947653874431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653874961","data":{"timestamp":" 947653874960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653877724","data":{"timestamp":" 947653877724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653880130","data":{"timestamp":" 947653880130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKACHOMEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653882141","data":{"timestamp":" 947653882141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653884089","data":{"timestamp":" 947653884089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653885949","data":{"timestamp":" 947653885949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653888006","data":{"timestamp":" 947653888006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAKATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653889484","data":{"timestamp":" 947653889484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653890200","data":{"timestamp":" 947653890200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653891748","data":{"timestamp":" 947653891748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653893743","data":{"timestamp":" 947653893743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMETAMETA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653895574","data":{"timestamp":" 947653895574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653897359","data":{"timestamp":" 947653897359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653899275","data":{"timestamp":" 947653899275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653900981","data":{"timestamp":" 947653900981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653902843","data":{"timestamp":" 947653902843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653905583","data":{"timestamp":" 947653905583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653907393","data":{"timestamp":" 947653907393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653909900","data":{"timestamp":" 947653909899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653911495","data":{"timestamp":" 947653911495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653913455","data":{"timestamp":" 947653913455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653915465","data":{"timestamp":" 947653915464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653915649","data":{"timestamp":" 947653915649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653954469","data":{"timestamp":" 947653954469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 60c05792-8099-446a-ae73-746ebea27d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653987002","data":{"timestamp":" 947653987002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 5db07602-86b7-4b31-883b-715e61f6463c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653990418","data":{"timestamp":" 947653990418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 5db07602-86b7-4b31-883b-715e61f6463c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653995052","data":{"timestamp":" 947653995052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 5db07602-86b7-4b31-883b-715e61f6463c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653995591","data":{"timestamp":" 947653995591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 5db07602-86b7-4b31-883b-715e61f6463c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653997467","data":{"timestamp":" 947653997467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 5db07602-86b7-4b31-883b-715e61f6463c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947653997492","data":{"timestamp":" 947653997492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072725"," gameId":" 5db07602-86b7-4b31-883b-715e61f6463c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}